好吧，让我们开始吧，这是分布式系统的682，所以
all right let's get started
this is 682 for distributed systems so
我想先简要说明一下我认为
I'd like to start with just a brief
explanation of what I think a
您知道分布式系统的核心是一组协作计算机
distributed system is you know the core
of it is a set of cooperating computers
通过网络相互通信以获得一些连贯的*
that are communicating with each other
over networked to get some coherent task
完成，因此我们将在本课程中重点介绍的各种示例
done and so the kinds of examples that
we'll be focusing on in this class are
大型网站的存储或MapReduce等大数据计算之类的东西
things like storage for big websites or
big data computations such as MapReduce
还有一些更奇特的事情，例如点对点文件共享
and also somewhat more exotic things
like peer-to-peer file sharing so
它们只是示例，我们将研究各种案例研究，
they're all just examples the kinds of
case studies we'll look at and the
所有这些都很重要的原因是，许多重要的基础设施
reason why all this is important is that
a lot of critical infrastructure out
分布式系统基础架构的建立需要
there is built out of distributed
systems infrastructure that requires
一台以上的计算机来完成工作，或者它本身就需要
more than one computer to get its job
done or it's sort of inherently needs to
被分散在身体上，所以人们为什么要建造这些东西的原因是
be spread out physically so the reasons
why people build this stuff so first of
在我谈论分布式系统之前，所有这些都提醒您您知道
all before I even talk about distributed
systems sort of remind you that you know
如果要重新设计系统，则需要解决一些问题
if you're designing a system redesigning
you need to solve some problem if you
可以在您知道的单台计算机上解决该问题，而无需构建
can possibly solve it on a single
computer you know without building a
分布式系统，您应该采用这种方式，并且可以完成很多工作
distributed system you should do it that
way and there's many many jobs you can
在一台计算机上完成工作，这总是更容易，所以分布式系统
get done on a single computer and it's
always easier so distributed systems you
知道在尝试构建分布式系统之前，您应该尝试其他所有方法
know you should try everything else
before you try building distributed
系统，因为它们不是，它们并不简单，所以人们之所以成为
systems because they're not they're not
simpler so the reason why people are
被驱使使用许多合作计算机，他们需要
driven to use lots of cooperating
computers are they need to get
高性能和思考方式是他们希望获得成就
high-performance and the way to think
about that is they want to get achieve
某种并行性很多CPU很多内存很多磁盘臂
some sort of parallelism lots of CPUs
lots of memories lots of disk arms
平行移动人们建造这些东西的另一个原因是能够
moving in parallel another reason why
people build this stuff is to be able to
容错
tolerate faults
如果两台计算机中的其中一台发生故障，您可以做两件事
have two computers do the exact same
thing if one of them fails you can cut
彼此之间是，一些问题只是自然而然地传播
over to the other one another is that
some problems are just naturally spread
像您知道要在银行间进行资金转帐或
out in space like you know you want to
do interbank transfers of money or
事情很好，您知道银行a在纽约市有这台计算机，而银行B在
something well you know bank a has this
computer in New York City and Bank B as
伦敦的这台计算机，您知道您只需为他们提供一些方式
this computer in London you know you
just have to have some way for them to
互相交谈并合作以实现目标，所以有一些
talk to each other and cooperate in
order to carry that out so there's some
一种自然的物理原因系统，其固有地在物理上
natural sort of physical reasons systems
that are inherently physically
分发的原因是人们建造此产品的最终目的是为了
distributed for the final reason that
people build this stuff is in order to
经常通过某种代码来实现某种安全目标
achieve some sort of security goal so
often by if there's some code you don't
信任，或者您知道您需要与某人互动，但您知道他们可能不需要
trust or you know you need to interact
with somebody but you know they may not
立即成为恶意软件，或者他们的代码中包含错误，因此您不想
be immediate malicious or maybe their
code has bugs in it so you don't want to
必须信任它，您可能想拆分计算，以便您知道自己的
have to trust it you may want to split
up the computation so you know your
东西在那里运行，那台计算机我的东西在这台计算机上运行，
stuff runs over there and that computer
my stuff runs here on this computer and
他们只与某种狭窄的狭窄定义的网络互相交谈
they only talk to each other to some
sort of narrow narrowly defined network
协议，假设我们可能担心您知道安全性，那就是
protocol assuming we may be worried
about you know security and that's
通过将事物拆分成多台计算机来实现
achieved by splitting things up into
multiple computers so that they can be
孤立本课程的大部分将与性能和故障有关
isolated the most of this course is
going to be about performance and fault
宽容，尽管其他两个人通常以某种方式
tolerance although the other two often
work themselves in by way of the sort of
我们要看的案例研究的约束条件
constraints on the case studies that
we're going to look at you know all
这些分布式系统，所以这些问题是因为它们有很多
these distributed systems so these
problems are because they have many
零件和零件同时执行，因为您有多台计算机
parts and the parts execute concurrently
because there are multiple computers you
解决并发编程带来的所有问题
get all the problems that come up with
concurrent programming all the sort of
复杂的交互，我们是时间相关的东西，这是一部分
complex interactions and we're
timing-dependent stuff and that's part
是什么使分布式系统变得困难？
of what makes distributed systems hard
another thing that makes distributed
系统之所以难，是因为您又拥有多个组件和一个网络，
systems hard is that because again you
have multiple pieces plus a network you
可能有非常意外的故障模式，即如果您有一个
can have very unexpected failure
patterns that is if you have a single
计算机，通常情况是计算机可以正常工作，或者崩溃或
computer it's usually the case either
computer works or maybe it crashes or
遭受电源故障或某些故障，但几乎可以正常工作或无效
suffers a power failure or something but
it pretty much either works or doesn't
由许多计算机组成的工作分布式系统，您可以部分
work distributed systems made up of lots
of computers you can have partial
某些零件的故障使其他人无法工作
failures that is some pieces stopped
working other people other pieces
继续工作，或者计算机正在工作，但是网络的某些部分
continue working or maybe the computers
are working but some part of the network
损坏或不可靠，因此部分故障是另一个原因
is broken or unreliable so partial
failures is another reason why
分布式系统很难，而造成这种困难的最后一个原因是您知道
distributed systems are hard and a final
reason why it's hard is that you know
他们构建分布式系统的最初原因通常是
them the original reason to build the
distributed system is often to get
更高的性能让您知道一千台计算机的性能价值
higher performance to get you know a
thousand computers worth of performance
或一千个磁盘臂的性能，但实际上
or a thousand disk arms were the
performance but it's actually very
要获得一千台计算机来加速一千个X的速度，将非常棘手
tricky to obtain that thousand X speed
up with a thousand computers there's
通常会有很多路障挡在您的路上，所以精灵需要小心一点
often a lot of roadblocks thrown in your
way so the Elven takes a bit of careful
设计使系统真正为您提供应有的性能
design to make the system actually give
you the performance you feel you deserve
因此，解决这些问题当然将完全取决于您
so solving these problems of course
going to be all about you know
解决这些问题之所以选择本课程，是因为通常
addressing these issues the reason to
take the course is because often the
问题和解决方案在技术上都非常有趣
problems and the solutions are quite
just technically interesting they're
对于其中一些困难的难题，有很好的解决方案，以
hard problems for some of these problems
there's pretty good solutions known for
其他问题不是很好的解决方案现在分布式系统
other problems they're not such great
solutions now distributed systems are
许多现实世界的系统都在使用它，例如经常涉及的大型网站
used by a lot of real-world systems out
there like big websites often involved
你知道大量的计算机，它们分布在一起
you know vast numbers computers that are
you know put together as distributed
我刚开始教这门课程时是分布式系统
systems when I first started teaching
this course it was distributed systems
是一种学术上的好奇心，你知道人们以为你知道
were something of an academic curiosity
you know people thought oh you know at a
有时它们被小规模使用，人们感到哦，总有一天他们会
small scale they were used sometimes and
people felt that oh someday they'd be
可能很重要，但现在特别受巨型网站的兴起所驱动
might be important but now particularly
driven by the rise of giant websites
你知道海量数据和整个装有计算机的仓库
that have you know vast amounts of data
and entire warehouses full of computers
在过去的二十年中，分布式系统已经变得非常
distributed systems in the last
twenty years have gotten to be very
计算基础架构的重要组成部分，这意味着
seriously important part of computing
infrastructure this means that there's
已经引起了他们的很多关注，但已经解决了很多问题，但是
been a lot of attention paid to them a
lot of problems have been solved but
还有很多未解决的问题，所以如果你是一名研究生
there's still quite a few unsolved
problems so if you're a graduate student
或您对研究感兴趣，但您遇到了很多麻烦
or you're interested in research there's
a lot to you let a lot of problems yet
在分布式系统中解决，您可以研究他的研究和
to be solved in distributed systems that
you could look into his research and
最后，如果您喜欢建造东西，这是一个很好的课程，因为它有一个实验室
finally if you like building stuff this
is a good class because it has a lab
您将构建一些相当现实的分布式系统的顺序
sequence in which you'll construct some
fairly realistic distributed systems
专注于性能和容错
focused on performance and fault
tolerance
所以你有很多练习建筑区，只是建筑分布
so you've got a lot of practice building
districts just building distributed
系统并使它们正常运行，让我稍微谈谈课程结构
systems and making them work all right
let me talk about course structure a bit
在我开始真正的技术内容之前，您应该能够找到
before I get started on real technical
content you should be able to find the
使用Google的课程网站，在课程网站上是实验室作业
course website using Google and on the
course website is the lab assignments
和课程表，还链接到广场页面，您可以在其中发布问题
and course schedule and also link to a
Piazza page where you can post questions
得到答案课程人员我是Robert Morris我将讲课
get answers the course staff I'm Robert
Morris I'll be giving the lectures I
你们也想站起来展示自己的脸，TAS也有
also have for TAS you guys want to stand
up and show your faces the TAS are
特别是在解决他们将要举行的实验室方面的专家
experts at in particular at doing the
solving the labs they'll be holding
办公时间，所以如果您对实验室有疑问，可以来
office hours so if you have questions
about the labs you can come you should
去上班时间，或者您可以向广场发表问题，课程内容包括
go to office hours or you could post
questions to Piazza the course has a
几个重要的组成部分之一是本次讲座，几乎有一篇论文
couple of important components one is
this lectures there's a paper for almost
每堂课都有两次考试
every lecture there's two exams
有实验室编程实验室，还有一个可选的最终项目，
there's the labs programming labs and
there's an optional final project that
您可以代替实验室之一
you can do instead of one of the labs
讲座将涉及分布式系统中的两个重要思想，它们也将是
the lectures will be about two big ideas
in distributed systems they'll also be a
一些关于实验室编程的讲座，很多
couple of lectures that are more about
sort of lab programming stuff a lot of
我们将通过很多案例研究来开展我们的讲座
our lectures will be taken up by case
studies a lot of the way that I sort of
尝试通过查看带出分布式系统的内容
try to bring out the content of
distributed systems is by looking at
论文，一些学者，一些由行业人士撰写，描述真实
papers some academics some written by
people in industry describing real
解决实际问题的方法
solutions to real problems
这些讲座实际上是录像带，我希望将它们在线发布
these lectures actually be videotaped
and I'm hoping to post them online so
这样，如果您不在这里，或者您想复习讲座，就可以
that you can so if you're not here or
you want to review the lectures you'll
能够再次看录像带讲座的论文，有一个
be able to look at the videotape
lectures the papers again there's one to
每周阅读大部分研究论文，其中一些是经典论文，例如
read per week most of a research paper
some of them are classic papers like
今天的论文，我希望你们中的一些人已经在MapReduce上阅读过
today's paper which I hope some of you
have read on MapReduce it's an old paper
但这是它激发了大量有趣工作的开始
but it was the beginning of its spurred
an enormous amount of interesting work
无论是学术界还是现实世界，都有些经典，有些则更多
both academic and in the real world so
some are classic and some are more
最近的论文都在谈论更多有关人的最新研究
recent papers sort of talking about more
up-to-date research what people are
目前很担心，从报纸上我们希望能弄明白什么
currently worried about and from the
papers we'll be hoping to tease out what
基本的问题是人们有哪些想法可能会或可能不会
the basic problems are what ideas people
have had that might or might not be
在解决分布式系统问题中很有用，我们有时会看
useful in solving distributed system
problems we'll be looking at sometimes
这些论文中有一些实施细节，因为其中很多
in implementation details in some of
these papers because a lot of this has
与基于软件的系统的实际构建有关，我们也
to do with actual construction of of
software based systems and we're also
要花一些时间看评估人们评估故障的程度
going to spend a certain time looking at
evaluations people evaluating how fault
通过衡量他们或人们衡量多少性能来容忍他们的系统
tolerant their systems by measuring them
or people measuring how much performance
还是他们根本没有提高性能，所以我希望
or whether they got performance
improvement at all so I'm hoping that
您上课之前会先阅读论文，演讲可能不会进行
you'll read the papers before coming to
class the lectures are maybe not going
如果您还没有阅读过该讲义，那将是非常有意义的，因为
to make as much sense if you haven't
already read the lecture because there's
没有足够的时间来解释论文的所有内容并进行整理
not enough time to both explaining all
the content of the paper and have a sort
对本文对在线课堂的意义进行了有趣的思考，所以您真的
of interesting reflection on what the
paper means online class so you really
在上课之前必须先阅读论文，希望其中之一
got to read the papers before I come
into class and hopefully one of the
您将在本课程中学习的内容是如何在鱼中快速阅读论文
things you'll learn in this class is how
to read a paper rapidly in the fish
并跳过那些可能不那么重要和关注的部分
and skip over the parts that maybe
aren't that important and sort of focus
在网站上发布重要想法时，每个链接都有
on teasing out the important ideas on
the website there's for every link to
购买时间表，有一个问题，您应该为此提交答案
buy the schedule there's a question that
you should submit an answer for for
我认为每篇论文的答案都应该在午夜到期，我们也请您
every paper I think the answers are due
at midnight and we also ask that you
通过网站同时提交您对论文的问题
submit a question you have about the
paper through the website in order both
在准备讲座时以及如果有的话给我一些思考的地方
to give me something to think about as
I'm preparing the lecture and if I have
时间，我将尝试通过电子邮件和至少回答一些问题
time I'll try to answer at least a few
of the questions by email and the
每个论文的前一天晚上午夜应有的问题和答案
question and the answer for each paper
due midnight the night before there's
两次考试我上次课堂会议上有一个期中考试
two exams there's a midterm exam in
class I think on the last class meeting
在春假之前，并且在期末考试的最后一周有期末考试
before spring break and there's a final
exam during final exam week at the end
这学期的考试主要集中在试卷和实验室
of the semester the exams are going to
focus mostly on papers and the labs and
可能是为他们做准备以及参加讲座和培训的最好方法
probably the best way to prepare for
them as well as attending lecture and
阅读试卷准备考试的一种好方法是查看我们所有的考试
reading the papers a good way to prepare
for the exams is to look at all exams we
与20年的旧考试和解决方案相关联，因此您可以查看这些内容和
have links to 20 years of old exams and
solutions and so you look at those and
感觉到我想问什么样的问题，确实
sort of get a feel for what kind of
questions that I like to ask and indeed
因为我们不可避免地会阅读许多相同的论文，每年我都会提出问题
because we read many of the same papers
inevitably I ask questions each year
就像过去几年实验室里提出的问题一样
that can't help but resemble questions
asked in previous years the labs there's
对于编程实验室，其中第一个实验室应在下周星期五进行。
for programming labs the first one of
them is due Friday next week lab one is
一个简单的MapReduce实验室，以实现您自己编写的论文版本
a simple MapReduce lab to implement your
own version of the paper they write
今天，我将在几分钟内讨论
today in which I'll be discussing in a
few minutes
实验2涉及使用一种称为“筏”的技术，以获取在
lab 2 involves using a technique called
raft in order to get fault taught in
为了在理论上允许某种排序，允许通过以下方式使任何系统容错
order to sort of allow in theory allow
any system to be made fault tolerant by
复制并使用此筏技术管理复制和
replicating it and having this raft
technique manage the replication and
管理某种类型的自动剪切，或者如果其中一个
manage sort of automatic cut
or if there's a field if one of the
复制的服务器发生故障，因此这是小伙子3中的rav4容错能力，您将使用
replicated servers fails so this is rav4
fault tolerance in lad 3 you'll use your
筏实施以构建容错键值服务器
raft implementation in order to build a
fault tolerant key-value server it'll be
在实验室4中进行复制并具有容错能力，您将获得复制的键值
replicated and fault tolerant in a lab 4
you'll take your replicated key-value
服务器并将其克隆到多个独立的组中，然后将
server and clone it into a number of
independent groups and you'll split the
所有这些个人中的键值存储系统中的数据
data in your key value storage system
across all of these individual
复制的组以通过运行多个复制得到并行加速
replicated groups to get parallel
speed-up by running multiple replicated
并行分组，您还将负责移动各种
groups in parallel and you'll also be
responsible for moving the various
不同服务器之间来来去去的大量数据而不会丢失任何数据
chunks of data between different servers
as they come and go without dropping any
球，这就是通常所说的分片键值服务分片
balls so this is a what's often called a
sharded key value service sharding
指拆分数据，将数据划分为多个
refers to splitting up the data
partitioning the data among multiple
服务器，以获取并行速度（如果需要），而不是进行实验4
servers in order to get parallel speed
up if you want instead of doing lab 4
您可以做一个自己选择的项目，这里的想法是，如果您有一些
you can do a project of your own choice
and the idea here is if you have some
您知道的一些分布式系统风格的分布式系统构想
idea for a distributed system you know
in the style of some of the distributed
如果您有自己的想法要在课堂上讨论的系统
systems we talked about in the class if
you have your own idea that you want to
追求，您喜欢构建某些东西并衡量它是否按顺序工作
pursue and you like to build something
and measure whether it worked in order
探索你的想法，你可以做一个项目，所以对于一个项目，你会选择
to explore your idea you can do a
project and so for a project you'll pick
一些队友，因为我们要求项目由两个或两个以上的团队完成
some teammates because we require that
projects are done in teams of two or
三个人，就像一些队友一样，将您的项目构想发送给我们，我们将
three people so like some teammates and
send your project idea to us and we'll
想一想，说是或否，也许给你一些建议，然后如果
think about it and say yes or no and
maybe give you some advice and then if
您继续进行，如果我们同意，您想做一个项目，那么您会做
you go ahead and do if we say yes and
you want to do a project you do that and
而不是实验4，这是在学期末完成的，你知道你会的
instead of lab 4 and it's due at the end
of the semester and you know you'll you
应该做一些设计工作并建立一个真实的系统，然后在
should do some design work and build a
real system and then in the last day of
课堂上，您将演示您的系统以及上交的简短内容
class you'll demonstrate your system
as well as handing in a short sort of
向我们发送有关您的建造情况的书面报告，我在网站上发布了一些
written report to us about what you
built and I posted on the website some
一些可能对您有用的想法
some ideas which might or may not be
useful for you to sort of spur thoughts
关于您可能会建立哪些项目，但实际上最好的项目是
about what projects you might build but
really the best projects are one where
你们对这个项目有一个好主意，主意是如果您想
sort of you have a good idea for the
project and the idea is if you want to
做一个项目，您应该选择一个与
do a project you should choose an idea
that's sort of in the same vein as the
本课中讨论的系统
systems that were talked about in this
class
好吧，回到实验室，实验室贪婪的是，我们会为您提供实验室代码
okay back to labs the lab Greed's they
we give you you hand in your lab code
我们针对它进行了一些测试，根据数量多少，您早就很棒
and we run some tests against it and
you're great early based on how many
您通过的测试，我们会为您提供所有我们使用的测试，而不是隐藏测试，因此如果
tests you pass we give you all the tests
that we use those no hidden tests so if
您实施了实验室，并且该实验室可靠地通过了所有测试，
you implement the lab and it reliably
passes all the tests and chances are
除非有有趣的事情发生，否则有时会很好
good unless there's something funny
going on which there sometimes is
如果您的鸡舍在运行时通过了所有测试，则很有可能
chances are good that if you your coop
passes all the tests when you run it or
通过所有测试，您将获得4分的满分，因此
pass all the tests when we run it and
you'll get a four score full score so
希望对您可能获得的分数没有任何神秘感
hopefully there'll be no mystery about
what score you're likely to get on the
实验室让我警告您，调试这些实验室可能很耗时，因为
labs let me warn you that debugging
these labs can be time-consuming because
他们是分布式系统，很多并发和通信
they're distributed systems and a lot of
concurrency and communication sort of
奇怪的难以调试的错误可能会出现，因此您真的应该开始
strange difficult to debug errors can
crop up so you really ought to start the
如果您被淘汰到最后，那么早期的实验室甚至不会带来很多麻烦
labs early don't don't even have a lot
of trouble if you be elapsed to the last
如果您有问题，请尽早开始，请到TAS办公室
moment you got to start early if your
problems please come to the TAS office
小时，请随时问有关广场和
hours and please feel free to ask
questions about the labs on Piazza and
的确，我希望如果您知道答案，您将回答人们的问题。
indeed I hope if you know the answer
that you'll answer people's questions on
广场也可以解决有关课程机制的任何问题，是的
Piazza as well all right any questions
about the mechanics of the course yes
所以问题是，这些因素如何影响不同因素
so the question is what is how does how
do the different factor these things
考虑到我忘记的成绩，但这一切都在网站的下面
factoring the grade I forget but it's
all on the it's on the website under
我认为虽然这是实验室中最重要的部分
something I think though it's the labs
are the single most important component
好的，这是一门有关应用程序基础结构的课程
okay alright so this is a course about
about infrastructure for applications
因此，在本课程中，我将以某种方式分裂
and so all through this course there's
going to be a sort of split in the way I
谈论应用程序之间的事情，这些人是其他人
talk about things between applications
which are sort of other people the
客户别人写的，但应用程序将使用
customer somebody else writes but the
applications are going to use the
我们在本课程中正在考虑的基础设施以及
infrastructure that we're thinking about
in this course and so the kinds of
基础架构往往会涉及到我们的存储通信和
infrastructure that tend to come up a
lot our storage communication and
计算，我们将讨论提供所有这三种类型的系统
computation and we'll talk about systems
that provide all three of these kinds of
基础架构的存储，事实证明，存储将成为一个
infrastructure the the storage it turns
out that storage is going to be the one
我们最关注的是因为它是定义非常明确且有用的抽象，
we focus most on because it's a very
well-defined and useful abstraction and
通常是相当简单的抽象，所以人们了解很多
usually fairly straightforward
abstraction so people know a lot about
如何构建如何使用和构建存储系统以及如何构建
how to build how to use and build
storage systems and how to build sort of
复制容错高性能分布式
replicated fault tolerant
high-performance distributed
存储的实现，我们还将讨论一些计算
implementations of storage we'll also
talk about some some of our computation
今天像MapReduce这样的系统是一个计算系统，我们将讨论
systems like MapReduce for today is a
computation system and we will talk
关于沟通的一些，但主要是从角度出发，这是我们需要的工具
about communications some but mostly
from the point is a tool that we need to
用于建立像计算机这样的分布式系统
use to build distributed systems like
computers have to talk to each other
通过网络，您知道您可能需要可靠性或其他一些东西，因此我们会
over a network you know maybe you need
reliability or something and so we'll
谈谈我们实际上主要是通信的使用者，如果您
talk a bit about what we're actually
mostly consumers of communication if you
想要了解通信系统，以了解它们如何工作
want to learn about communication
systems as sort of how they work that's
更多的主题是六个八到九个，因此用于存储和计算的很多
more the topic of six eight to nine
so for storage and computation a lot of
我们的目标是能够发现使用简化的抽象
our goal is to be able to discover
abstractions where use of simplifying
这两个存储和计算分布式存储的接口，以及
the interface to these two storage and
computation distributed storage and
计算基础架构，以便在其之上轻松构建应用程序
computation infrastructure so that it's
easy to build applications on top of it
真正的意思是我们需要我们能够建立
and what that really means is that we
need to we'd like to be able to build
隐藏这些系统的分布式性质的抽象，因此
abstraction that hide the distributed
nature of these of these systems so the
梦想几乎无法完全实现，但梦想是能够建立
dream which is rarely fully achieved but
the dream would be to be able to build
查找应用程序的接口是非分布式的
an interface that looks to an
application is if it's a non distributed
存储系统就像一个文件系统或每个人已经存在的东西
storage system just like a file system
or something that everybody already
知道如何编程，并具有我们很想成为的非常简单的模型语义
knows how to program and has a pretty
simple model semantics we'd love to be
能够构建外观和行为类似于非分布式存储的界面
able to build interfaces that look and
act just like non distributed storage
和计算系统，但实际上您知道巨大的超高性能
and computation systems but are actually
you know vast extremely high performance
下面的容错分布式系统，所以我们都有抽象
fault tolerant distributed systems
underneath so we both have abstractions
而且您知道，随着课程的进行，我们知道您只有一部分
and you know as you'll see as a course
goes on we sort of you know only part of
很少会找到分布式版本的抽象
the way there it's rare that you find an
abstraction for a distributed version of
具有简单行为的存储或计算，但他就像非
storage or computation that has simple
behavior but he's just like the non just
每个人都可以理解但人们得到的非分布式存储版本
non distributed version of storage that
everybody understands but people getting
在这方面更好，我们将尝试研究人们的方式和方法
better at this and we're gonna try to
study the ways and what people have
学会了有关构建这样的抽象的知识，所以是什么样的主题
learned about building such abstractions
ok so what kind of what kind of topics
出现是因为我们正在考虑将这些抽象作为第一个
show up is we're considering these
abstractions the first one this first
常规主题，我们将看到很多我们研究过的系统
topic general topic that we'll see a lot
a lot of the systems we looked at have
与实现有关，例如，您经常看到的那种工具
to do with implementation so for example
the kind of tools that you see a lot for
人们学习如何构建这些系统的方式就是远程过程
for ways people learn how to build these
systems are things like remote procedure
呼叫的目标是掩盖事实
call
whose goal is to mask the fact that
我们正在通过不可靠的网络交流另一种实现方式
we're communicating over an unreliable
Network another kind of implementation
我们将看到很多的主题是线程，这是一种编程技术，
topic that we'll see a lot is threads
which are a programming technique that
允许我们利用允许我们利用多核计算机的东西，但是也许
allows us to harness what allows us to
harness multi-core computers but maybe
对于此类而言，更重要的是一种构造并发的方法
more important for this class threads
are a way of structuring concurrent
希望可以简化程序员对这些视图的看法
operations in a way that's hopefully
simplifies the programmer view of those
并发操作，并且因为我们要大量使用线程，所以事实证明
concurrent operations and because we're
gonna use threads a lot it turns out
我们还需要从实施级别开始
we're going to need to also you know
just as from an implementation level
花一些时间思考并发控制之类的事情
spend a certain amount of time thinking
about concurrency control things like
锁以及这些实现想法将出现在的主要位置
locks and the main place that these
implementation ideas will come up in the
课堂上，它们会在许多论文中涉及到，但是你会面子
class they'll be touched on in many of
the papers but you're gonna come face
在构建分布式数据库所需的实验室中，这一切的面目都很大
the face of all this in a big way in the
labs you need to build distributed you
知道做分布式系统的编程，这很像
know do the programming for distributed
system and these are like a lot of sort
除了普通的编程之外，您还知道一些重要的工具
of important tools you know beyond just
sort of ordinary programming these are
构建分布式系统所需的一些关键工具
some of the critical tools that you'll
need to use to build distributed systems
我们将要讨论的所有论文中提到的另一个重要主题是
another big topic that comes up in all
the papers we're going to talk about is
性能通常，构建分布式系统的高级目标是
performance usually the high-level goal
of building a distributed system is to
得到人们所谓的可扩展性加速，因此我们正在寻找可扩展性和
get what people call scalable speed-up
so we're looking for scalability and
我所说的可伸缩性或可伸缩加速是指如果我遇到问题
what I mean by scalability or scalable
speed-up is that if I have some problem
我正在用一台计算机解决问题，然后购买了第二台计算机来帮助我执行
that I'm solving with one computer and I
buy a second computer to help me execute
我的问题是，如果我现在可以在一半时间内解决问题，或者也许可以解决
my problem if I can now solve the
problem in half the time or maybe solve
每分钟在两台计算机上知道的问题实例是我在计算机上的两倍
twice as many problem instances you know
per minute on two computers as I had on
那就是可扩展性的一个例子
one then that's an example of
scalability so
你知道计算机或资源让我知道两次
sort of two times you know computers or
resources gets me you know two times
性能或吞吐量，如果您可以构建一个系统，这将是一个巨大的锤子
performance or throughput and this is a
huge hammer if you can build a system
那实际上就是这种行为Namie，如果您增加
that actually has this behavior Namie
that if you increase the number of
您因某种原因而引发问题的计算机，您得到的因素更多
computers you throw at the problem by
some factor you get that factor more
从系统中吞吐更多性能，这是一个巨大的胜利，因为您可以
throughput more performance out of the
system that's a huge win because you can
用钱正确地购买计算机，而如果为了获得
buy computers with just money right
whereas if in order to get the
替代方法是，为了获得更高的性能，您必须付出代价
alternative to this is that in order to
get more performance you have to pay
程序员重组您的软件以获得更好的性能
programmers to restructure your software
to get better performance to make it
更有效率或应用某种专门技术更好的算法
more efficient or to apply some sort of
specialized techniques better algorithms
或者如果您必须付钱给程序员来修复您的代码
or something if you have to pay
programmers to fix your code to be
更快，这是一条昂贵的路要走，我们希望能够
faster that's an expensive way to go
we'd love to be able just oh by thousand
计算机而不是十台计算机，吞吐量提高了一百倍
computers instead of ten computers and
get a hundred times more throughput
这太棒了，因此这种可扩展性想法在
that's fantastic and so this sort of
scalability idea is a huge idea in the
人们喜欢建立大型网站之类的东西时的后脑勺
backs of people's heads when they're
like building things like big websites
如果继续运行，您是否知道要建立完整的计算机
that run on are you know building full
of computers if the building full of
那里的计算机可以获得相应的性能，但是
computers is there to get a sort of
corresponding amount of performance but
您必须谨慎设计才能真正得到
you have to be careful about the design
in order to actually get that
性能如此常见，当我们查看图表或我正在
performance so often the way this looks
when we're looking at diagrams or I'm
在本课程中编写图表是因为我不认为我们正在构建一个
writing diagrams in this course is that
I'm not supposing we're building a
通常，您可能拥有一个您知道具有HTTP服务器的网站
website ordinarily you might have a
website that you know has a HTTP server
假设它有某些类型的用户
let's say it has some types of users
许多网络浏览器，并且它们与运行Python或PHP或其他功能的网络服务器通信
many web browsers and they talk to a web
server running Python or PHP or whatever
某种Web服务器，并且Web服务器与某种数据库对话
sort of web server and the web server
talks to some kind of database
你知道当你有一个或两个用户时，你可以只运行一台计算机
you know when you have one or two users
you can just have one computer running
两者，也许是用于Web服务器的计算机，也可能是来自数据库的计算机
both and maybe a computer for the web
server and a computer from the database
但也许突然之间，您会真正受到欢迎，并且您会起床并
but maybe all of a sudden you get really
proper popular and you'll be up and
您是否知道1亿人注册了您的服务ID
you've you know 100 million people sign
up your service ID how do you how do you
一定可以解决您的问题，它可以在一台计算机上支持数百万人
fix your c-certainly can it support
millions of people on a single computer
除非经过非常仔细的劳动密集型优化，但是您
except by extremely careful
labor-intensive optimization but you
通常没有时间进行加速
don't have time for so typically the way
you're going to speed things up the
您要做的第一件事是购买更多的Web服务器，然后拆分用户，以便
first thing you do is buy more web
servers and just split the user so that
您知道用户访问网络服务器1的用户或用户的比例很少
you know how few users or some fraction
the user go to a web server 1 and the
另一半您将它们发送到Web服务器2，因为也许您正在构建我
other half you send them to a web server
2 and because maybe you're building I
不知道什么Reddit或所有用户都需要看到相同的东西
don't know what reddit or something
where all the users need to see the same
数据最终，所有Web服务器都与后端通信，并且您可以
data ultimately you have all the web
servers talk to the backend and you can
继续在这里添加Web服务器很长时间，因此这是一种
keep on adding web servers for a long
time here and so this is a way of
如果您正在运行，则可以并行提高Web服务器代码的速度
getting parallel speed up on the web
server code you know if you're running
PHP或Python也许效率不高，只要每个单独的网站
PHP or Python maybe it's not too
efficient as long as each individual web
服务器不会在数据库上增加太多负载，您可以添加很多网站
server doesn't put too much load on the
database you can add a lot of web
服务器，然后再遇到问题，但是这种可伸缩性很少
servers before you run into problems but
this kind of scalability is rarely
不幸的是，无限的肯定不是没有认真的思考等等。
infinite unfortunately certainly not
without serious thought and so what
这些系统往往会发生在您拥有10个或
tends to happen with these systems is
that at some point after you have 10 or
现在突然有20或100个Web服务器都与同一个数据库通信
20 or 100 web servers all talking to the
same database now all of a sudden the
数据库开始成为瓶颈，添加更多Web服务器不再有帮助
database starts to be a bottleneck and
adding more web servers no longer helps
因此，您难得有全面的能力来分类无限数量的
so it's rare that you get full scale
ability to sort of infinite numbers of
添加无限数量的计算机有时会耗尽您的电量，因为
adding infinite numbers of computers
some point you run out of gas because
您添加更多计算机的位置不再是瓶颈
the place at which you are adding more
computers is no longer the bottleneck by
拥有很多Web服务器，我们基本上消除了瓶颈
having lots and lots of web servers we
basically moved the bottleneck
我认为这限制了从Web服务器到数据库的性能，
I think it's limiting performance from
the web servers to the database and at
这一点实际上您几乎肯定需要做一些设计工作，因为
this point actually you almost certainly
have to do a bit of design work because
很少有您能采取任何直接方法
it's rare that you can
there's any straightforward way to take
单个数据库并使用它来重构事物，或者您可以获取数据
a single database and sort of refactor
things with it or you can take data
在单个数据库中排序并重构它，以便将其拆分为多个数据库
sorta in a single database and refactor
it so it's split over multiple databases
但这通常是相当多的工作，而且因为它很笨拙，但是人们很多
but it's often a fair amount of work and
because it's awkward but people many
人们实际上需要这样做，我们将在其中看到很多例子
people actually need to do this we're
gonna see a lot of examples in this
人们谈论的分布式系统的课程是存储
course in which the distributed system
people are talking about is a storage
系统，因为作者正在运行，所以您知道类似大型网站的信息
system because the authors were running
you know something like a big website
无论如何，在单个数据库或存储服务器上用尽了所有电量，因此
that ran out of gas on a single database
or storage servers anyway so the
可扩展性的故事是我们喜欢构建以这种方式扩展的系统，但您知道
scalability story is we love to build
systems that scale this way but you know
很难实现或取消工作并进行设计工作以推动这一想法
it's hard to make it or takes work off
and design work to push this idea
无限远，所以出现的另一个大话题是容错
infinitely far ok so another big topic
that comes up a lot is fault tolerance
如果您要构建的系统中只有一台计算机，那么
if you're building a system with a
single computer in it well a single
电脑经常可以工作很多年，就像我的办公室里有服务器那样
computer often can stay up for years
like I have servers in my office that
已经运行了好几年没有崩溃，您知道计算机非常可靠
have been up for years without crashing
you know the computer is pretty reliable
可靠的操作系统显然是我的建筑物的力量
the operating systems reliable
apparently the power in my building is
非常可靠，因此拥有单台计算机并不少见，这只是一个
pretty reliable so it's not uncommon to
have single computers it's just a for
但是，如果要从成千上万个系统中构建系统，那将是惊人的时间
amazing amount of time however if you're
building systems out of thousands of
则即使每台计算机预计可以使用一年时间
computers then even if each computer can
be expected to stay up for a year with a
千台计算机，这意味着您将拥有大约三台计算机
thousand computers that means you're
going to have like about three computer
您的一千台计算机中每天的故障数量如此之多
failures per day in your set of a
thousand computers so solving big
大型分布式系统的问题变成了非常罕见的容错能力
problems with big distributed systems
turns sort of very rare fault tolerance
非常真实的故障非常罕见的故障问题转化为故障问题
very real failure very rare failure
problems into failure problems that
在拥有一千台计算机的系统中几乎总是发生
happen just all the time in a system
with a thousand computers there's almost
当然总是有东西坏了，总是有一些计算机或者
certainly always something broken it's
always some computer that's either
崩溃或神秘，您知道运行不正确或缓慢或执行错误
crashed or mysteriously you know running
incorrectly or slowly or doing the wrong
东西，也许有一部分网络，我们有一千台计算机
thing or maybe there's some piece of the
network with a thousand computers we got
很多网络电缆和很多网络交换机，所以您知道
a lot of network cables and a lot of
network switches and so you know there's
总是有人踩到的某些网络电缆不可靠，或者
always some network cable that somebody
stepped on and is unreliability or
掉线的网络电缆或某些风扇损坏的网络，并且
network cable that fell out or some
networks which whose fan is broken and
开关过热并发生故障，其中总是存在一些小问题
the switch overheated and failed there's
always some little problem somewhere in
您的建筑物大小的分布式系统，如此之大，从根本上解决了问题
your building sized distributed system
so big scale turns problems from very
罕见的事件，您不必真正担心那么多
rare events you really don't have to
worry about that much into just constant
问题意味着失败必须是真实的，或者响应必须掩盖
problems that means the failure has to
be really or the response the masking of
失败的能力而没有失败只是必须建立在
failures the ability to proceed without
failures just has to be built into the
设计，因为总是有失败，而且您知道这是构建您的一部分
design because there's always failures
and you know it's part of building you
为我们真正需要的应用程序程序员了解方便的抽象
know convenient abstractions for
application programmers we really need
但要尽可能建立基础设施
that but to be able to build
infrastructure that as much as possible
对应用程序程序员隐藏故障或掩盖故障之类的东西
hides the failures from application
programmers or masks them or something
这样每个应用程序程序员都不必拥有完整的
so that every application programmer
doesn't have to have a complete
对于可能发生的所有各种故障的复杂故事
complicated story for all the different
kinds of failures that can occur there's
一堆关于错误的含义的不同概念
a bunch of different notions that you
can have about what it means to be fault
容忍多一点，但你确切地知道我们的意思是，
tolerant about a little more but you
know exactly what we mean by that we'll
看到很多不同的口味，但在更常见的想法中，
see a lot of a lot of different flavors
but among the more common ideas you see
一个是可用性，所以您知道某些系统的设计使其在某些情况下
one is availability so you know some
systems are designed so that under some
某种特定类型的故障并非所有故障，而是某些特定类型的故障
kind certain kinds of failures not all
failures but certain kinds of failures
尽管出现故障，系统仍将继续运行，同时告知您
the system will keep operating despite
the failure while providing you know
完好无损的服务，即使是
undamaged service the same kind of
service it would have provided even if
没有失败，所以从某种意义上说，有些系统可用
there had been no failure so some
systems are available in that sense that
你知道，所以如果你建立一个复制服务，也许有两个
up and up you know so if you build a
replicated service that maybe has two
您知道其中一个副本副本服务器失败的副本可能失败
copies you know one of the replicas
replica servers fail fails maybe the
其他服务器可以继续运行，但它们都失败了，当然不能
other server can continue operating
they both fail of course you can't you
知道在这种情况下您无法保证可用性，因此可用系统通常
know you can't promise availability in
that case so available systems usually
在某些失败情况下说得很好，我们将继续提供
say well under certain set of failures
we're going to continue providing
服务，我们将可以使用的故障比发生的更多
service we're going to be available more
failures than that occur it won't be
可以再使用另一种容错能力
available anymore
another kind of fault tolerance you
可能除了可用性之外，或者除了可用性之外，还可能
might you might have or in addition to
availability or by itself as
可恢复性，这意味着如果出现问题，可能
recoverability and what this means is
that if something goes wrong maybe the
服务将停止工作，只是停止响应请求
service will stop working that it is
it'll simply stop responding to requests
它会等待有人来修复或发生任何问题
and it will wait for someone to come
along and repair or whatever went wrong
但是修复之后，系统将能够继续运行，好像什么也没有发生
but after the repair occurs the system
will be able to continue as if nothing
不好的地方错了，所以这比
bad had gone wrong right so this is sort
of a weaker requirement than
可用性，因为在此期间我们不会做任何事情
availability because here we're not
going to do anything while while the
直到出现故障的组件被修复为止，否则我们
failed come until the failed component
has been repaired but the fact that we
可以不知道就起床再去，但又不会失去正确性
can get up get going again without you
know but without any loss of correctness
仍然是一个重要的要求，这意味着您知道可恢复的系统
is still a significant requirement it
means you know recoverable systems
通常需要做一些事情，例如将最新日期保存在磁盘等上
typically need to do things like save
their latest date on disk or something
当电源恢复后，他们可以在哪里找回它
where they can get it back
you know after the power comes back up
甚至在可用系统之间，以使系统在实际中有用
and even among available systems in
order for a system to be useful in real
生活通常是可用系统SPECT的方式是
life usually what the way available
systems are SPECT is that they're
如果发生过多的故障，则直到出现一定数量的故障才可用
available until some number of failures
have happened if too many failures have
发生可用系统将停止工作，或者您知道将停止响应
happened an available system will stop
working or you know will stop responding
根本没有，但是只要修复了足够的东西，它就会继续运行，因此
at all but when enough things have been
repaired it'll continue operating so a
良好的可用系统在某种程度上也可以恢复
good available system will sort of be
recoverable as well in a sensitive to
发生许多失败，它将停止回答，但随后会
many failures occur
it'll stop answering but then will
之后继续正确进行，所以这就是我们的爱-这就是我们想要的
获得最大的锤子，我们将看到解决这些问题的多种方法
obtain the biggest hammer what we'll see
a number of approaches to solving these
问题实际上是最重要的工具
problems there's really sort of
things that are the most important tools
我们在这个部门中有一个是非易失性存储
we have in this department one is
non-volatile storage so that you know
崩溃电源故障或建筑物范围内发生的任何电源故障
something crash power fails or whatever
there's a building wide power failure we
可以使用非易失性存储，就像硬盘驱动器，闪存或固态存储
can use non-volatile store it's like
hard drives or flash or solid-state
驱动器或某种用于存储检查点或状态日志的东西
drives or something to sort of store a
check point or a log of the state of a
系统，然后在电源恢复供电或有人维修我们的电源时
system and then when the power comes
back up or somebody repairs our power
供应商注意到我们将能够从硬盘读取最新状态
suppliers notice what we'll be able to
read our latest state off the hard drive
并从那里继续，所以一种工具是非易失性存储，
and continue from there so so one tool
is sort of non-volatile storage and the
非易失性存储的管理Ning出现了很多，因为非易失性
management of non-volatile storage just
Ning comes up a lot because non-volatile
存储往往更新成本很高，因此，大量的
storage tends to be expensive to update
and so a huge amount of the sort of
构建高性能容错系统的本质
nitty-gritty of building sort of
high-performance fault-tolerant systems
您知道可以避免写非易失性存储的聪明方法
is in you know clever ways to avoid
having to write the non-volatile storage
在过去甚至今天都太多了，你知道写非易失性是什么
too much in the old days and even today
you know what writing non-volatile
存储意味着要移动磁盘臂并等待磁盘旋转
storage meant was moving a disk arm and
waiting for a disk platter to rotate
两者在您所知的范围内都非常缓慢
both of which are agonizingly slow on
the scale of you know three gigahertz
微处理器的美好事物，例如闪存寿命要好很多，但仍然
microprocessors good things like flash
life is quite a bit better but still
需要大量的思想才能获得良好的性能，而另一个则是
requires a lot of thought to get good
performance out of and the other big
我们用于容错的工具是复制和管理
tool we have for fault tolerance is
replication and the management of
复制副本有点棘手，您知道隐藏在其中的问题
replicated copies is sort of tricky you
know that sort of he problem lurking in
任何复制的系统，其中我们有两个服务器，每个服务器假定都相同
any replicated system where we have two
servers each with a supposedly identical
系统状态副本出现的关键问题始终是这两个
copy of the system state the key problem
that comes up is always that the two
副本将意外地偏离同步状态，并且将不再是副本
replicas will accidentally drift out of
sync and will stop being replicas right
这就是您所知道的每个设计背后的内容
and this is just you know with the back
of the every design that we're gonna see
使用复制来获得容错能力和实验室-很多-都是
for using replication to get fault
tolerance and lab - a lot - you're all
有关用于容错的复制副本的管理管理
about management management of
replicated copies for fault tolerance
如您所见，它非常复杂
as you'll see it's pretty complex a
最终主题最终交叉主题是一致性，因此这是我所举的例子
final topic final cross-cutting topic is
consistency so it's an example of what I
假设我们正在构建分布式存储系统，这就是一致性
mean by consistency supposing we're
building a distributed storage system
而且它是键/值服务，因此它仅支持两个操作，也许有一个
and it's a key/value service so it just
supports two operations maybe there's a
进行操作，然后给它一个键和一个值，然后存储系统进行排序
put operation and you give it a key and
a value and that the storage system sort
的藏匿值，因为此键的值保持它只是一个
of stashes away the value under as the
value for this key maintains it's just a
很大的键和值表，然后客户端就可以很好地进行操作了
big table of keys and values and then
there's a good operation you the client
向其发送密钥，并且应该知道存储服务，请使用
sends it a key and the storage service
is supposed to you know respond with the
它已为该密钥权限存储的值的值，这很好
value of the value it has stored for
that key right and this is kind of good
当我无法想到其他任何东西作为分布式系统的示例时
when I can't think of anything else as
an example of a distributed system all
哦，没有键值服务，它们非常有用，就是
Oh without key value services and
they're very useful right they're just
当然是一种基本的简单版本的存储系统
sort of a kind of fundamental simple
version of a storage system so of course
如果您是应用程序程序员，那么这两种操作对您很有帮助
if you're an application programmer it's
helpful if these two operations kind of
具有相关的含义，您可以阅读手册和手册
have meanings attached to them that you
can go look in the manual and the manual
说你知道这是什么意思如果电话打对了你会得到什么
says you know what it what it means what
you'll get back if you call get right
一切对您而言意味着什么，请立即放好，以便立即
and sort of what it means for you to
call put all right so it's immediate so
某种规格说明他们的意思，例如谁知道你怎么能
some sort of spec for what they meant
otherwise like who knows how can you
可能在编写应用程序时未说明put get是什么
possibly write an application without a
description of what putting get are
应该要做的，这是一致性的主题，也是为什么
supposed to do and this is the topic of
consistency and the reason why it's
分布式系统中有趣的是，无论是性能还是故障
interesting in distributed systems is
that both for performance and for fault
容忍的原因容错的原因我们经常有多个副本
tolerant reasons fault tolerance reason
we often have more than one copy of the
数据随处可见，因此您可以在非分布式系统中
data floating around so you know in a
non distributed system where you just
有一个带有单个表的服务器，虽然不是总是，但是
have a single server with a single table
there's often although not always but
人们对布丁的接受程度通常相对没有歧义
there's often like relatively no
ambiguity about what pudding get could
可能意味着对李先生的权利，你知道认罪的意思是
possibly mean right in
to ative Lee you know what put means is
更新表，获取的意思就是获取存储在其中的版本
update the table and what get means is
just get me the version that's stored in
该表，但是在分布式系统中存在多个副本
the table which but in a distributed
system where there's more than one copy
由于复制或缓存或谁知道可能会有什么原因
in the data due to replication or
caching or who knows what there may be
此键值对有很多不同的版本，就像一个
lots of different versions of this key
value pair floating around like if one
如果假设某些客户端发行了一份副本，您知道该副本的数量，并且您知道
of the replicas you know if supposing
some client issues a put and you know
服务器有两个副本，所以它们都有正确的键值表
there's two copies of the the server so
they both have a key value table right
也许关键之一对他们两个都有价值20，然后一些客户问题
and maybe key one has value twenty on
both of them and then some client issues
一个不错的看跌期权，我们在这里有客户，它将发送一个要更新的看跌期权
a put nice we have client over here and
it's gonna send a put it wants to update
一个21的值好吧，也许这是在计算东西
the value of one to be twenty-one all
right maybe it's counting stuff in this
密钥值服务器发送带有密钥一和值二十一的看跌期权，将其发送到
key value server so sends a put with key
one and value twenty one it sends it to
第一台服务器，它将发送您知道要更新的同一个put
the first server and it's about to send
the same put you know wants to update
两个副本都正确，这会使它们保持同步，这将要发送此认沽权，但是
both copies right it keeps them in sync
it's about to send this put but just
在将其发送到第二台服务器之前，我崩溃了或掉电了
before it sends to put to the second
server crashes I power failure or bug an
操作系统之类的东西，所以现在可悲的是，我们发送了
operating system or something so now the
state were left in sadly is that we sent
这个看跌期权，所以我们更新了两个副本之一，没有价值二十
this put and so we've updated one of the
two replicas didn't have value twenty
一个，但另一个仍然有二十个，现在有人来读
one but the other ones still with twenty
now somebody comes along and reads with
得到，他们可能得到他们想要读取与键一相关联的值
a get and they might get they want to
read the value associated with key one
他们可能会得到二十一，或者他们可能会得到二十，这取决于他们与谁交谈
they might get twenty one or they might
get twenty depending on who they talk to
即使是规则，如果您总是
and even if the rule is you always talk
to the top server first if you're
建立容错系统实际规则必须是
building a fault-tolerant system the
actual rule has to be oh you talk to the
除非失败，否则首先是顶级服务器
top server first unless it's failed in
which case you talk to the bottom server
因此，无论哪种方式，总有一天您可能会冒险将这种陈旧的数据副本暴露给某些
so either way someday you risk exposing
this stale copy of the data to some
未来再次可能是许多人得到了更新的二十一，然后像
future again it could be that many gets
get the updated twenty one and then like
下周突然有些收益，你知道一个星期的副本
next week all of a sudden some get
yields you know a week old copy of the
数据，所以不是很一致，所以顺序，但是您知道
data so that's not very consistent
right so in order but you know it's the
可能会发生的事情我们不小心，所以您知道我们需要
kind of thing that could happen right
we're not careful so you know we need to
我们是否需要实际写下有关看跌期权的规则，
have we need to actually write down what
the rules are going to be about puts and
由于复制而受到这种危险，事实证明
gets given this danger of due to
replication and it turns out there's
您可以拥有许多不同的一致性定义，您知道其中许多是
many different definitions you can have
of consistency you know many of them are
相对简单，其中许多听起来像是我得到了你
relatively straightforward many of them
sound like well I get yields the you
知道最近完成的看跌期权的看跌期权价值，所以
know value put by the most recently
completed put all right so that's
通常被称为强一致性，事实证明，构建它也非常有用
usually called strong consistency it
turns out also it's very useful to build
例如，那里的一致性较弱的系统不会
systems that have much weaker
consistency there for example do not
保证像get这样的东西都能看到最新put和
guarantee anything like a get sees the
value written by the most recent put and
原因是他们通常拥有非常一致的系统
the reason so there's there strongly
consistent systems they usually have
一些版本可以看到最新的看跌期权，尽管您必须做很多
some version that gets seen most recent
puts although you have to there's a lot
要解决的细节还有每周一致的多种口味
of details to work out there's also
weekly consistent many sort of flavors
每周不进行任何此类保证的系统
of weekly consistent systems that do not
make any such guarantee that you know
可以保证你知道如果有人进行认沽，那么你可能看不到
may guarantee well you're you know if
someone does a put then you may not see
看跌期权，您可能会看到看跌期权未更新的旧值
the put you may see old values that
weren't updated by the put for an
无限的时间，也许是人们非常感兴趣的原因
unbounded amount of time maybe and the
reason for people being very interested
在小麦一致性方案中，具有Rezac的强一致性
in wheat consistency schemes is that
strong consistency that is having Rezac
蔡承租人一定会看到最新的权利
Chua lessee be guaranteed to see the
most recent right that's a very
实施昂贵的规范，因为这意味着您几乎可以肯定
expensive spec to implement because what
it means is almost certainly that you
必须有人必须做很多沟通才能真正
have to somebody has to do a lot of
communication in order to actually
如果有多个副本，请实施一些具有高度一致性的概念
implement some notion of strong
consistency if you have multiple copies
这意味着作者或读者，或者也许两者都要咨询
it means that either the writer or the
reader or maybe both has to consult
在这种情况下，每一个副本都可能导致客户端崩溃，
every copy like in this case where you
know maybe a client crash left one
已更新，但如果要实施强大的功能，则不会更新其他内容
updated but not the other if we wanted
to implement strong
西塞顿（Sisseton）在他们看来，在这个系统中，我们可能会让读者阅读
Sisseton see in them maybe a simple way
in this system we'd have readers read
两份副本，或者如果有多个副本，则所有副本均使用
both of the copies or if there's more
than one copy all the copies and use the
他们发现的最新书面价值，但价格昂贵，很多
most recently written value that they
find but that's expensive that's a lot
之所以要读取一个值，是为了避免尽可能多地交流
of chitchat to read one value so in
order to avoid communication as much as
可能尤其如此，如果复制品距离很远，人们会建立薄弱的系统，
possible particularly if replicas are
far away people build weak systems that
在这种情况下，实际上可能允许过时地读取旧值，尽管
might actually allow the stale read of
an old value in this case although
通常会有更多的语义关联到这些较弱的方案中
there's often more semantics attached to
that to try to make these weak schemes
更有用，我们是您知道强大的一致性的沟通问题
more useful and we're this communication
problem you know strong consistency
需要昂贵的沟通，这确实使您陷入麻烦
requiring expensive communication where
this really runs you into trouble is
如果我们将复制用于容错，那么我们真的想要
that if we're using replication for
fault tolerance then we really want the
具有独立故障概率的副本具有不相关的故障
replicas to have independent failure
probability to have uncorrelated failure
因此，例如，将我们的数据的两个副本都放在相同的伊拉克
so for example putting both of the
replicas of our data in the same iraq in
在同一个机房​​中，这可能是一个非常糟糕的主意
the same machine room it's probably a
really bad idea
因为如果有人通过电源线绊到那个机架，我们的两个副本
because if someone trips over the power
cable to that rack both of our copies of
我们的数据将消失，因为它们都连接到相同的电源
our data are going to die because
they're both attached to the same power
在同一机架中连接电缆，因此在搜索中将副本作为独立的
cable in the same rack so in the search
for making replicas as independent and
为了获得体面的容错能力，人们可能会喜欢失败
failure as possible in order to get
decent fault tolerance people would love
将不同的副本尽可能地分开，例如在不同的城市或
to put different replicas as far apart
as possible like in different cities or
也许在大陆的相对两侧，所以一场地震摧毁了一个数据
maybe on opposite sides of the continent
so an earthquake that destroys one data
中心极不可能破坏其他数据中心
center will be extremely unlikely to
also destroy the other data center that
作为您知道的另一个副本，因此我们很乐意能够做到这一点
as the other copy you know so we'd love
to be able to do that if you do that
然后另一个副本在数千英里之外
then the other copy is thousands of
miles away and the rate at which light
行驶意味着可能需要数毫秒或数十倍的时间
travels means that it may take on the
order of milliseconds or tens of
毫秒以与整个非洲的数据中心进行通信，以便
milliseconds to communicate to a data
center across the continent in order to
更新数据的另一个副本，以便进行通信
update the other copy of the data and so
that makes this the communication
强一致性所需的，可能极度良好的一致性
required for strong consistency for good
consistency potentially extremely
就像每次您想做其中一件歌剧一样昂贵
expensive like every time you want to do
one of these put opera
或再次取决于您的实施方式，您可能必须坐在那里
or maybe again depending on how you
implement it you might have to sit there
等待大约10或20或30毫秒才能与对方通话
waiting for like 10 or 20 or 30
milliseconds in order to talk to both
数据副本，以确保它们都已更新或已检查
copies of the data to ensure that
they're both updated or or both checked
要找到最新的副本，那笔巨额费用是10或
to find the latest copy and that
tremendous expense right this is 10 or
在20或30毫秒的机器上，毕竟我将执行十亿
20 or 30 milliseconds on machines that
after all I'll execute like a billion
每秒的指令数，因此我们在浪费大量潜在指令的同时
instructions per second so we're wasting
a lot of potential instructions while we
等待人们经常使用弱得多的系统，您只能更新
wait people often go much weaker systems
you're allowed to only update the
最近的副本，您只查询了最近的副本，我的意思是说有很大的一种
nearest copy you're only consulted
nearest copy I mean there's a huge sort
如何构造弱点的学术研究和现实世界研究
of amount of academic and real-world
research on how to structure weak
一致性保证，因此它们实际上对应用程序以及
consistency guarantees so they're
actually useful to applications and how
充分利用它们，以便获得高性能
to take advantage of them in order to
actually get high performance alright so
这是该课程中技术思想的闪电预览
that's a lightning preview of the
technical ideas in the course any
在我开始谈论MapReduce之前，我对此有疑问
questions about this before I start
talking about MapReduce all right I want
切换到Map Reduce实际上是一种详细的案例研究
to switch to Map Reduce that's a sort of
detailed case study that's actually
将说明我们现在在这里谈论的大多数想法
going to illustrate most of the ideas
that we've been talking about here now
产生最初由Google I设计和制造并使用的系统
produces a system that was originally
designed and built and used by Google I
认为该论文可以追溯到2004年，他们面临的问题是
think the paper dates back to 2004 the
problem they were faced with was that
他们在TB和TB的数据上运行大量计算，例如
they were running huge computations on
terabytes and terabytes of data like
创建网络所有内容的索引或分析链接
creating an index of all of the content
of the web or analyzing the link
整个网络的结构以便识别最重要的页面或
structure of the entire web in order to
identify the most important pages or the
您所知道的最权威的页面整个网络在当时都是如此
most authoritative pages as you know the
whole web is what's even in those days
Web的数十兆字节的数据构建索引基本上相当于一个
tens of terabytes of data building index
of the web is basically equivalent to a
您可以合理地对整个数据进行排序
sort running sort of the entire data
sort you know ones like reasonably
昂贵，并且按照我一直以来的方式对整个内容进行排序
expensive and to run a sort on the
entire content to the way I've been a
单台计算机要花多长时间，但您知道
single computer
how long would have taken but you know
是数周，数月或数年之类的时间，所以Google当时是
it's weeks or months or years or
something so Google the time was
迫切希望能够对成千上万的海量数据进行海量计算
desperate to be able to run giant
computations on giant data on thousands
的计算机，以便计算可以快速完成它是
of computers in order that the
computations could finish rapidly it's
值得他们购买大量计算机，以便他们的工程师
worth it to them to buy lots of
computers so that their engineers
无需花费大量时间阅读报纸或其他内容
wouldn't have to spend a lot of time
reading the newspaper or something
等待他们的大型计算机工作完成，因此有一段时间
waiting for their big compute jobs to
finish and so for a while they had their
聪明的工程师或手写体，您知道是否需要编写网络
clever engineer or sort of handwrite you
know if you needed to write a web
索引器或某种类型的林肯会花费您知道的Google眨眼分析工具
indexer or some sort of Lincoln outlay a
blink analysis tool you know Google
买了电脑，他们说在这里你知道的工程师会写，但是从不
bought the computers and they say here
engineers you know do write but never
您在这些计算机上喜欢的任何软件，您都知道他们会
whatever software you like on these
computers and you know they would
费力地编写一种一次性的手动咬软件
laborious ly write the sort of one-off
manually bitten software to take
他们正在解决的任何问题，以某种方式将其大量耕种
whatever problem they were working on
and so to somehow farm it out to a lot
的计算机，并组织该计算并取回数据（如果您
of computers and organize that
computation and get the data back if you
只雇用熟练的分布式系统专家的工程师，也许那是
only hire engineers who are skilled
distributed systems experts maybe that's
好的，尽管即使那样可能还是很浪费工程工作，但是他们
ok although even then it's probably very
wasteful of engineering effort but they
想要雇用在其他方面很有技巧的人
wanted to hire people who were skilled
at something else and not necessarily
想花所有时间编写分布式系统软件的工程师
engineers who wanted to spend all their
time writing distributed system software
所以他们确实需要某种框架，以使其易于
so they really needed some kind of
framework that would make it easy to
只是让他们的工程师写下他们想要的任何分析的胆量
just have their engineers write the kind
of guts of whatever analysis they wanted
就像排序算法或Web索引或链接分析器一样
to do like the sort algorithm or a web
index or link analyzer or whatever just
编写该应用程序的胆量而无法在数千个应用程序上运行
write the guts of that application and
not be able to run it on a thousands of
电脑而不必担心如何分散工作的细节
computers without worrying about the
details of how to spread the work over
数以千计的计算机如何组织数据移动
the thousands of computers how to
organize whatever data movement was
需要如何应对不可避免的失败，所以他们正在寻找
required how to cope with the inevitable
failures so they were looking for a
框架，使非专业人员可以轻松编写和
framework that would make it easy for
non specialists to be able to write and
运行大型分布式计算，这就是MapReduce的全部意义
run giant distributed computations and
so that's what MapReduce is all about
想法是程序员只是编写应用程序设计器
and the idea is that the programmer just
write the application designer
这种分布式计算的使用者，我只能够编写一个简单的Map
consumer of this distributed computation
I'm just be able to write a simple map
什么都不知道的函数和简单的reduce函数
function and a simple reduce function
that don't know anything about
发行版和MapReduce框架将负责其他所有事项，因此
distribution and the MapReduce framework
would take care of everything else so an
假设MapReduce所做的工作的抽象视图是通过假设
abstract view of how what MapReduce is
up to is it starts by assuming that
有一些输入，输入被分成几整堆
there's some input and the input is
split up into some a whole bunch of
不同的文件或数据块，以某种方式，所以我们在想，不，是的，您知道
different files or chunks in some way so
we're imagining that no yeah you know
输入文件一，放置文件二，以此类推，您知道这些输入也许是您知道的网络
input file one and put file two etc you
know these inputs are maybe you know web
从网络爬网的页面或更可能包含的大文件
pages crawled from the web or more
likely sort of big files that contain
许多网站，每个网站都包含许多从网络抓取的网络文件，
many web each of which contains many web
files crawl from the web all right and
Map Reduce的开始方式是您要查找Map
the way Map Reduce
starts is that you're to find a map
函数，MapReduce框架将在每个
function and the MapReduce framework is
gonna run your map function on each of
输入文件，当然您可以在这里看到一些明显的
the input files and of course you can
see here there's some obvious
可用的并行性可以并行运行这些映射，因此每个映射
parallelism available can run the maps
in parallel so the each of these map
函数仅看起来像此输入，并产生输出，该输出为Map
functions only looks as this input and
produces output the output that a map
需要产生的功能是一个列表，您知道它需要一个文件作为输入
function is required to produce is a
list you know it takes a file as input
文件是输入数据的一部分，它会生成一个密钥列表
and the file is some fraction of the
input data and it produces a list of key
值对作为map函数的输出，例如，让我们假设
value pairs as output the map function
and so for example let's suppose we're
编写最简单的MapReduce示例单词计数MapReduce工作目标
writing the simplest possible MapReduce
example a word count MapReduce job goal
是计算每个单词出现的次数，因此您的Map功能可能
is to count the number of occurrences of
each word so your map function might
发出键值对，其中键是单词，值只是一个，所以
emit key value pairs where the key is
the word and the value is just one so
对于C处的每个单词，则此映射函数会将输入拆分为
for every word at C so then this map
function will split the input up into
单词或其他地方，它发出该单词作为键，并发出1作为
words or everywhere ditzies
it emits that word as the key and 1 as
该值，然后再将所有这些值累加，以获得
the value and then later on will count
up all those ones in order to get the
最终输出，所以您知道输入1包含单词
final output so you know maybe input 1
has the word
里面有a，里面有单词B，因此Map要生​​成的输出是
a in it and the word B in it and so the
output the map is going to produce is
密钥A值一个密钥B值一个可能第二个不能通信看到文件
key a value one key B value one maybe
the second not communication sees a file
它里面有一个B，别无其他，所以它将实现输出b1
that has a B in it and nothing else so
it's going to implement output b1 maybe
第三个输入中有一个A和一个C，所以我们运行所有这些映射
this third input has an A in it and a C
in it alright so we run all these maps
在所有输入文件上，我们通过纸质电话获得此中间件
on all the input files and we get this
intermediate with the paper calls
中间输出，对于每个映射都是一组键值对作为输出
intermediate output which is for every
map a set of key value pairs as output
然后计算的第二阶段是运行约简，想法是
then the second stage of the computation
is to run the reduces and the idea is
MapReduce框架从的所有Map中收集所有实例
that the MapReduce framework collects
together all instances from all maps of
每个关键字，以便MapReduce框架将所有
each key word so the MapReduce framework
is going to collect together all of the
您会从每张Map中知道每个键值对为a的键值对
A's you know from every map every key
value pair whose key was a it's gonna
收集全部并交给他们
take collect them all and hand them to
程序员一个电话来寻找归约函数，然后
one call of the programmer to find
reduce function and then it's gonna take
所有的B并收集在一起，当然，您知道需要一个真正的
all the B's and collect them together of
course you know requires a real
收集，因为它们是密钥B的不同实例，由
collection because they were different
instances of key B were produced by
在不同的计算机上显示Map的不同指示，所以我们不在谈论
different indications of map on
different computers so we're not talking
关于数据移动的信息，所以我们要收集所有B键并将其交给
about data movement I'm so we're gonna
collect all the B keys and hand them to
不同的reduce调用具有所有B键作为其参数，并且相同
a different call to reduce that has all
of the B keys as its arguments and same
作为C，因此MapReduce框架将安排一个
as C so there's going to be the
MapReduce framework will arrange for one
调用以减少出现在任何数学输出中的每个键，并且
call to reduce for every key that
occurred in any of the math output and
您知道我们这类愚蠢的字数示例
you know for our sort of silly word
count example all these reduces have to
做或其中任何一个要做的只是计算传递给它的项目数
do or any one of them has to do is just
count the number of items passed to it
甚至不必查看这些项目，因为它知道每个项目都是
doesn't even have to look at the items
because it knows that each of them is
这个词是负责加一是你不必看的价值
the word is responsible for plus one is
the value you don't have to look at
我们只计算的那些，因此减少将产生一个和
those ones we've just count
so this reduce is going to produce a and
然后减少其输入的数量，它将产生关联的密钥
then the count of its inputs this reduce
it's going to produce the key associated
与它，然后计数它的值也是两个，所以这是一个
with it and then count of its values
which is also two so this is what a
典型的MapReduce作业看起来很高级，只是为了完整性
typical MapReduce job looks like the
high level just for completeness the
好一点的术语，整个计算称为工作
well some a little bit of terminology
the whole computation is called the job
MapReduce的任何调用都称为任务，因此我们拥有整个工作，并且
anyone invocation of MapReduce is called
a task so we have the entire job and
它由一堆数学任务然后再由一堆产生的任务组成
it's made up of a bunch of math tasks
and then a bunch of produced tasks so
这是这个字数的一个例子，您知道什么是Map并减少
it's an example for this word count you
know the what the map and reduce
函数看起来像map函数将值作为键
functions would look like the map
function takes a key in the value as
参数，现在我们正在谈论像用普通语言编写的函数
arguments and now we're talking about
functions like written in an ordinary
诸如C ++或Java之类的编程语言，或者谁知道呢，所以这仅仅是代码
programming language like C++ or Java or
who knows what so this is just code
普通人可以写一个用于字数统计的map函数的功能是
people ordinary people can write what a
map function for word count would do is
拆分键是通常被忽略的文件名，我们真的很在乎
split the the key is the file name which
typically is ignored we really care what
文件名是，而V是此Map输入文件的内容，因此V为
the file name was and the V is the
content of this maps input file so V is
你知道只是包含所有这些文本，我们将V分解为单词，然后
you know just contains all this text
we're gonna split V into words and then
每个字
for each word
我们只是要发出和发出需要两个参数的手套，您知道冷静地可以
we're just gonna emit and emit takes two
arguments mitts you know calmly map can
生成发射由MapReduce框架提供，我们通过手工生成来生成
make emit is provided by the MapReduce
framework we get to produce we hand emit
一个是单词的键，一个是字符串one的值，就是这样
a key which is the word and a value
which is the string one so that's it for
map函数和单词计数map函数以及MapReduce的字面意思是
the map function and a word count map
function and MapReduce literally it
可能就这么简单，所以就有了使
could be this simple
so there's sort of promise to make the
而且您知道此Map功能对分配或
and you know this map function doesn't
know anything about distribution or
多台计算机或我们需要的事实，我们需要跨网络移动数据
multiple computers or the fact we need
we need to move data across the network
或谁知道这是非常简单的
or who knows what
this is extremely straightforward and
减少单词数的reduce函数，用已知的方式调用记得
the reduce function for a word count the
reduce is called with you know remember
每个reduce都会通过调用给定键的所有实例进行排序
each reduce is called with sort of all
the instances of a given key on the
MapReduce框架调用通过其负责的键以及一个
MapReduce framework calls reduce with
the key that it's responsible for and a
映射产生的与该键关联的所有值的向量
vector of all the values that the maps
produced associated with that key the
关键是这个词是所有值，我们在这里不喜欢它们，我们只是
key is the word the values are all ones
we don't like here about them we only
关心它们的数量，因此reduce具有其自己的省略功能
care about how many they were and so
reduce has its own omit function that
只是将要发出的值作为最终输出作为this的值
just takes a value to be emitted as the
final output as the value for the this
关键，所以我们要承认这个数组的长度，所以这也大约是
key so we're gonna admit a length of
this array so this is also about as
最简单的reduce函数具有，并且在Map Reduce中非常简单
simplest reduce functions have are and
in Map Reduce namely extremely simple
并且不需要有关容错的知识或其他任何东西
and requiring no knowledge about fault
tolerance or anything else alright any
有关基本框架的问题是
questions about the basic framework yes
[音乐]
[Music]
你的意思是你能提供减速器的输出吗？
you mean can you feed the output of the
reducers sort of oh yes oh yes in in in
在现实生活中可以在现实生活中正常
in real life all right
in real life it is routine among
您知道的MapReduce用户定义了一个MapReduce作业，该作业需要一些输入并
MapReduce users to you know define a
MapReduce job that took some inputs and
产生一些输出，然后执行第二个MapReduce作业，您知道自己
produce some outputs and then have a
second MapReduce job you know you're
做一些非常复杂的多阶段分析或迭代算法，例如
doing some very complicated multistage
analysis or iterative algorithm like
例如PageRank，这是Google用于排序的算法
PageRank for example which is the
algorithm Google uses to sort of
估算不同网页的重要性或影响力
estimate how important or influential
different webpages are that's an
迭代算法是一种逐渐收敛于答案的算法，如果您
iterative algorithm is sort of gradually
converges on an answer and if you
我认为他们最初是在MapReduce中实现的，您必须运行
implement in MapReduce which I think
they originally did you have to run the
MapReduce作业多次，并且每个作业的输出都是您所知道的
MapReduce job multiple times and the
output of each one is sort of you know
网页列表，其中每个列表的值，权重或重要性都有更新
list of webpages with an updated sort of
value or weight or importance for each
网页，因此通常将其输出然后用作输入
webpage so it was routine to take this
output and then use it as the input to
另一个MapReduce工作哦，是的，您需要对这些东西进行设置
another MapReduce job oh yeah well yeah
you need to sort of set things up the
输出，您需要对知识的简化功能进行评分
output you need to rate the reduced
function sort of in the knowledge that
哦，我需要生成格式或所需信息的数据
oh I need to produce data that's in the
format or as the information required
对于下一个MapReduce工作，我的意思是这实际上带来了
for the next MapReduce job I mean this
actually brings up a little bit of a
MapReduce框架的缺点，如果
shortcoming in the MapReduce framework
which is it's great if you are if the
您需要运行的算法很容易表示为数学运算
algorithm you need to run is easily
expressible as a math followed by this
按键排序数据，然后进行归约操作，仅此而已
sort of shuffling of the data by key
followed by a reduce and that's it
我的MapReduce非常适合可以这种形式转换的算法，
my MapReduce is fantastic for algorithms
that can be cast in that form and we're
此外，每张Map都必须完全独立，并且
furthermore each of the maps has to be
completely independent and
必须是纯功能性功能
are required to be functional pure
functional functions that just look at
他们的论点，没有别的，你知道这就像一个限制
their arguments and nothing else
you know that's like it's a restriction
事实证明，许多人想要运行更长的管道
and it turns out that many people want
to run much longer pipelines that
涉及很多不同类型的处理，而MapReduce可以帮助您
involve lots and lots of different kinds
of processing and with MapReduce you
必须将来自多个MapReduce的拼凑起来
have to sort of cobble that together
from multiple MapReduce distinct
MapReduce作业和更高级的系统，我们将在稍后的内容中进行讨论。
MapReduce jobs and more advanced systems
which we will talk about later in the
当然可以更好地让您指定完整的管道
course are much better at allowing you
to specify the complete pipeline of
计算，它们会进行优化，您知道框架可以实现所有
computations and they'll do optimization
you know the framework realizes all the
您要做的事情和组织更复杂的事情要有效地进行优化
stuff you have to do and organize much
more complicated efficiently optimize
更复杂的计算
much more complicated computations
从程序员的角度来看，这只是映射和减少
from the programmers point of view it's
just about map and reduce from our point
的观点将是关于工作进程和工作服务器
of view it's going to be about the
worker processes and the worker servers
它们是MapReduce框架的一部分，其中包括许多其他内容
that that are they're part of MapReduce
framework that among many other things
调用Map并简化函数，所以从我们的角度来看，我们关心
call the map and reduce functions so
yeah from our point of view we care a
关于周围框架如何组织的很多事情
lot about how this is organized by the
surrounding framework this is sort of
程序员认为所有分发内容都被剥夺了
the programmers view with all the
distributive stuff stripped out yes
抱歉，我要再说一遍哦，你的意思是即时数据在哪里可以
sorry I gotta say it again oh you mean
where does the immediate data go okay so
有两个问题，一个是当您致电MIT时，数据发生了什么，
there's two questions one is when you
call a MIT what happens to the data and
另一个是功能运行的地方
the other is where the functions run so
实际的答案是，首先烂掉的东西有很多说法
the actual answer is that first where
the stuff rotten there's a number of say
一千台服务器，实际上这里要看的是图一
a thousand servers um actually the right
thing to look at here is figure one in
在现实世界中，坐在这下面的纸有很多收藏
the paper sitting underneath this in the
real world there's some big collection
服务器，我们称它们为工作服务器或工作服务器，
of servers and we'll call them maybe
worker servers or workers and there's
也是一个主服务器，用于组织整个计算和
also a single master server that's
organizing the whole computation and
这里发生的是主服务器，知道知道有一些
what's going on here is the master
server for know knows that there's some
您知道的输入文件数5000个输入文件
number of input files you know five
thousand input files and it farms out in
将Map假期发送给其他工作人员，以便它将消息发送给
vacations of map to the different
workers so it'll send a message to
工人七说请运行，您知道该Map功能
worker seven saying please run you know
this map function on such-and-such an
输入文件，然后是worker函数，这是MapReduce的一部分，
input file and then the worker function
which is you know part of MapReduce and
完全了解Map Reduce，然后读取文件，读取输入内容
knows all about Map Reduce well then
read the file read the input whatever
不论输入哪个文件，然后以文件名值作为参数调用此映射函数
whichever input file and call this map
function with the file name value as its
论据，然后工人进程将雇员在其中实现什么，
arguments then that worker process will
employees what implements in it and
每次map调用发出工作进程时，都会将此数据写入文件中
every time the map calls emit the worker
process will write this data to files on
本地磁盘，因此映射发生了什么，并且它们会在
the local disk so what happens to map
emits and is they produce files on the
映射工作人员正在累积所有键和值的本地光盘
map workers local discs that are
accumulating all the keys and values
由Map产生的结果在该工作程序上运行，因此在数学阶段结束时
produced by the maps run on that worker
so at the end of the math phase what
我们剩下的是所有这些工人机器，它们的输出是
we're left with is all those worker
machines each of which has the output of
一些在该工作机上运行的Map，然后是MapReduce
some of whatever maps were run on that
worker machine then the MapReduce
工作人员安排将数据移动到需要的位置
workers arrange to move the data to
where it's going to be needed for the
减少这样的结果，因为在典型的大型计算中您知道这一点
reduces so and since and a you know in a
typical big computation you know this
这种减少指示将需要所有的Map输出
this reduce indication is going to need
all map output that
提到了钥匙a，但事实证明，这是一个简单的例子
mentioned the key a but it's gonna turn
out you know this is a simple example
但可能通常每个Map指示都会产生很多
but probably in general every single map
indication will have produce lots of
键，包括键a的某些实例，因此通常在我们什至还没有顺序之前
keys including some instances of key a
so typically in order before we can even
运行作为MapReduce工作程序的MapReduce框架的reduce函数
run this reduce function the MapReduce
framework that is the MapReduce worker
在我们千台服务器中运行的一台将不得不与每台服务器进行对话
running on one of our thousand servers
is going to have to go talk to every
千台服务器中的另一台，说你知道我要运行
single other of the thousand servers and
say look you know I'm gonna run the
减少密钥，请查看存储在您的
reduce for key a please look at the
intermediate map output stored in your
磁盘并找出密钥a的所有实例，然后通过网络发送它们
disk and fish out all of the instances
of key a and send them over the network
对我来说，reduce worker要做的就是从每个人那里获取
to me so the reduce worker is going to
do that it's going to fetch from every
负责它负责的所有密钥实例
worker all of the instances of the key
that it's responsible for that the
主人告诉它要负责，一旦收集到所有数据
master has told it to be responsible for
and once it's collected all of that data
那么它可以调用reduce，而reduce函数本身调用reduce可以忽略
then it can call reduce and the reduce
function itself calls reduce omit which
与其中的映射不同，减少辐射所做的是写输出
is different from the map in it and what
reduces emit does is writes the output
到Google使用的群集文件服务中的文件，所以这是我
to a file in a cluster file service that
Google uses so here's something I
没有提到我没有提到输入生活在哪里以及
haven't mentioned I haven't mentioned
where the input lives and where the
输出生活都是文件，因为我们想要的任何输入
output lives they're both files because
any piece of input we want the
能够读取任何工作服务器上任何输入的灵活性，这意味着
flexibility to be able to read any piece
of input on any worker server that means
我们需要某种网络文件系统来存储输入数据，因此确实
we need some kind of network file system
to store the input data and so indeed
本文讨论了称为GFS或Google文件系统的事物，而GFS是
the paper talks about this thing called
GFS or Google file system and GFS is a
集群文件系统和BFS实际上在完全相同的一组工作器上运行
cluster file system and BFS actually
runs on exactly the same set of workers
能够自动运行MapReduce和输入GFS的服务器
that work our servers that run MapReduce
and the input GFS just automatically
当您知道这是一个文件系统时，您可以在我的文件中读取它
when you you know it's a file system you
can read in my files it just
自动将您存储在其中的任何大文件拆分到许多服务器上，
automatically splits up any big file you
store on it across lots of servers and
64 MB的块，因此如果您查看10 TB的已爬网内容，则进行写操作
64 megabyte chunks so if you write
if you view of ten terabytes of crawled
网页内容，您只需将它们作为单个大文件写入GFS
web page contents and you just write
them to GFS even as a single big file
GFS会自动将大量数据拆分为64 KB
GFS will automatically split that vast
amount of data up into 64 kilobyte
块均匀地分布在所有GFS服务器上，也就是说所有
chunks distributed evenly over all of
the GFS servers which is to say all the
Google提供的服务器，这真是太棒了
servers that Google has available and
that's fantastic that's just what we
如果需要，然后我们要运行一个MapReduce作业，该作业将整个已爬网的网站
need if we then want to run a MapReduce
job that takes the entire crawled web as
输入数据的存储方式已经在所有
input the data is already stored in a
way that split up evenly across all the
服务器，这意味着您知道的Map工作人员将向您启动
servers and so that means that the map
workers you know we're gonna launch you
知道我们是否有一千台服务器，每个服务器将启动一千名Map工作者
know if we have a thousand servers we're
gonna launch a thousand map workers each
在输入数据上读取一个1000s，他们将能够读取
reading one 1000s at the input data and
they're going to be able to read the
来自一千个GFS文件服务器的并行数据，因此变得越来越庞大
data in parallel from a thousand GFS
file servers thus getting now tremendous
您知道的通读总吞吐量为一千台服务器
total read throughput you know the read
through put up a thousand servers
所以您是否认为Google当中有一组物理机器
so so are you thinking maybe that Google
has one set of physical machines among
GFS和运行MapReduce作业的一组单独的物理机可以
是的，所以问题是这里的箭头实际上涉及什么？
right so the question is what does this
arrow here actually involve and the
回答说，实际上这些年来，随着Google
answer that actually it sort of changed
over the years as Google's
涉及这个系统，但是如果我们有
involve this system but you know what
this in those general case if we have
大型文件存储在某些大型网络文件系统中，就像GFS一样
big files stored in some big Network
file system like you know it's like GFS
有点像您可能在雅典娜上使用过的AFS，在那里您可以与
is a bit like AFS you might have used on
Athena where you go talk to some
收集，然后将数据拆分到大收集o服务器上
到网络上的那些服务器以在这种情况下检索您的数据
to those servers over the network to
retrieve your data in that case what
此箭头可能表示Meta MapReduce worker进程必须关闭
this arrow might represent is the meta
MapReduce worker process has to go off
并通过网络与正确的GFS服务器或可能与
and talk across the network to the
correct GFS server or maybe servers that
存储它作为输入的一部分，并通过网络将其获取到MapReduce
store it's part of the input and fetch
it over the network to the MapReduce
工人机器才能通过Map，这当然是最通用的
worker machine in order to pass the map
and that's certainly the most general
案例，这最终是MapReduce在世界上实际运作的方式
case and that was eventually how
MapReduce actually worked in the world
但是如果您这样做的话，那将是很多网络
of this paper though and and if you did
that that's a lot of network
交流中您正在谈论10 TB的数据，而我们已经移走了10 TB
communication are you talking about ten
terabytes of data and we have moved 10
TB的数据中心网络（您知道数据中心）
terabytes across their data center
network which you know data center
网络每秒需要千兆比特，但移动数十万比特仍需要很多时间
networks wanting gigabits per second but
it's still a lot of time to move tens of
兆兆字节的数据，以便尝试并确实在本文的世界中
terabytes of data in order to try to and
indeed in the world of this paper in
2004年，MapReduce系统中最受限制的瓶颈是网络
2004 the most constraining bottleneck in
their MapReduce system was Network
吞吐量，因为它们在网络上运行，如果您可以阅读到
throughput because they were running on
a network if you sort of read as far as
评估部分他们的网络他们的网络因为他们有成千上万
the evaluation section their network
their network as was they had thousands
机器
of machines
无论如何，他们会收集机器，他们会插入机器，你知道
whatever and they would collect machines
they would plug machines and you know
每个机架的机器，您都知道该机架的以太网交换机或
each rack of machines and you know an
Ethernet switch for that rack or
某事，但是然后您知道他们都需要互相交谈，但是有
something but then you know they all
need to talk to each other but there was
与所有落基山脉都是与之通信的网络交换机的路由以太网交换机，
a route Ethernet switch that all of the
Rockies are net switches talked to and
这一点，您知道，所以如果您只选择一些Map Reduce工作人员和一些GFS
this one and you know so if you just
pick some Map Reduce worker and some GFS
服务器，您知道机会至少是之间通信时间的一半
server you know chances are at least
half the time the communication between
他们必须通过这个不会改变他们的路线
them has to pass through this one
wouldn't switch their routes which had
总吞吐量只有一些，我忘了你知道一些
only some amount of total throughput
which I forget you know some number of
每秒千兆字节，我忘记了这个数字，但是当我进行除法运算时
gigabits per second and I forget the
number well but when I did the division
被除以路由中可用的总吞吐量
that is divided up to the total
throughput available in the routes which
他们在论文中使用的大约2000台服务器进行了实验
by the roughly 2000 servers that they
used in the papers experiments what I
得到的是路由交换机或整个网络的每台机器共享
got was that each machine share of the
route switch or of the total network
在其设置中，每秒50兆位的容量仅为每秒50兆位
capacity was only 50 megabits per second
per second in their setup 50 megabits
每台机器每秒，然后看起来好像很多50兆位天哪
per second per machine and then might
seem like a lot 50 megabits gosh
数百万，但与磁盘的速度相比实际上很小
millions and millions but it's actually
quite small compared to how fast a disks
罗恩（Ron）或CPU在运行，因此其网络每秒50兆位的速度是
Ron or CPUs run and so this with their
network this 50 megabits per second was
就像一个巨大的极限，所以他们真的站在
like a tremendous limit and so they
really stood on their heads in the
论文中描述的设计避免使用网络，他们发挥了
design described in the paper to avoid
using the network and they played a
避免在可能的情况下通过网络发送内容的一系列技巧
bunch of tricks to avoid sending stuff
over the network when they possibly
可以避免它之一，就是他们将运行gfs服务器，并且
could avoid it one of them was they
would they ran the gfs servers and the
MapReduce工人在同一组机器上，因此他们有一千
MapReduce workers on the same set of
machines so they have a thousand
运行GFS的计算机，他们在那千台上实现了GFS服务
machines they'd run GFS they implement
their GFS service on that thousand
机器，然后在同一千台机器上运行MapReduce，然后
machines and run MapReduce on the same
thousand machines and then when the
师父将Map工作拆分开来，然后将其耕种到不同的地方
master was splitting up the map work and
sort of farming it out to different
当它要运行将要运行的Map时，会很聪明
workers it would cleverly when it was
about to run the map that was going to
从输入文件中读取一个文件，它将从GFS找出哪个服务器实际持有
read from input file one it would figure
out from GFS which server actually holds
输入文件一个在其本地磁盘上，它将发送该输入文件的映射
input file one on its local disk and it
would send the map for that input file
到同一台计算机上的MapReduce软件，因此默认情况下，此箭头
to the MapReduce software on the same
machine so that by default this arrow
实际上是从本地磁盘读取的本地本地，并且不涉及
was actually local local read from the
local disk and did not involve the
网络，您会根据故障或负载或其他原因知道
network and you know depending on
failures or load or whatever that
不能总是这样做，但是几乎所有Map都可以在同一Map上运行
couldn't always do that but almost all
the maps would be run on the very same
机器并存储数据，从而为他们节省了大量时间
machine and stored the data thus saving
them vast amount of time that they would
否则，必须等待下一个技巧才能在网络上移动输入数据
otherwise had to wait to move the input
data across the network the next trick
他们玩过的Map就是我之前提到的Map，并将此输出存储在本地
they played is that map as I mentioned
before stores this output on the local
您在其上运行Map的计算机的磁盘，以便再次存储
disk of the machine that you run the map
on so again storing the output of the
Map不需要网络通讯，他不是立即
map does not require network
communication he's not immediately
因为输出存储在磁盘中，但是我们肯定知道一种方法或
because the output stored in the disk
however we know for sure that one way or
以便通过MapReduce的方式将所有您知道的人分组在一起
another in order to group together all
of you know by the way the MapReduce is
定义以便将与给定关联的所有值组合在一起
defined in order to group together all
of the values associated with the given
密钥并将它们传递给单个调用以在某台机器上进行生产
key and pass them to a single invocation
to produce on some machine this is going
需要网络通信，我们将要知道我们需要获取
to require network communication we're
gonna you know we want to need to fetch
所有托架，并给他们一台必须在
all bays and give them a single
machine that have to be moved across the
网络，所以这种洗牌的运动是一种
network and so this shuffle this
movement of the keys from is kind of
最初按行存储在运行Map的同一台机器上，我们需要它们
originally stored by row and on the same
machine that ran the map we need them
本质上是将要存储在机器上的列上
essentially to be stored on by column on
the machine that's going to be
负责减少行存储的这种转换
responsible for reduce this
transformation of row storage
从本质上讲，列存储被称为纸质，称为洗牌，实际上
essentially column storage is called the
paper calls a shuffle and it really that
需要从Map上跨网络移动所有数据，
required moving every piece of data
across the network from the map that
减少到需要它的程度，现在就像昂贵的
produced it to the reduce that would
need it and now it's like the expensive
是MapReduce的一部分
part of the MapReduce yeah
你是对的，你可以想象一个更不同的定义
you're right you can imagine a different
definition in which you have a more kind
流减少我不知道我没有想到这一点
of streaming reduce I don't know I
haven't thought this through I don't
知道为什么就程序员而言那是否可行
know why whether that would be feasible
or not certainly as far as programmer
界面就像是他们的第一目标的目标是
interface like if the goal their
number-one goal really was to be able to
那些不知道发生了什么的人可以很容易地进行编程
make it easy to program by people who
just had no idea of what was going on in
系统，所以您可能知道这个斑点，这实际上是减少
the system so it may be that you know
this speck this is really the way reduce
函数的外观，您在C ++或类似的流式版本中就知道了
functions look and you know in C++ or
something like a streaming version of
现在开始看起来我不知道看起来如何可能不是这个
this is now starting to look I don't
know how it look probably not this
符号，但您知道也许可以那样做，实际上许多现代
symbol but you know maybe it could be
done that way and indeed many modern
系统人们对现代事物的了解变得更加复杂
systems people got a lot more
sophisticated with modern things that
是MapReduce的后续产品，它们确实涉及处理
are the successors the MapReduce and
they do indeed involve processing
数据流通常不是批量处理方法，而是批量处理
streams of data often rather than this
very batch approach there is a batch
从某种意义上说，我们等待直到获得所有数据，然后进行处理
approach in the sense that we wait until
we get all the data and then we process
因此首先必须要有一个有限输入的概念
it so first of all that you then have to
have a notion of finite inputs right
现代系统通常确实可以让您流媒体，并且能够
modern systems often do indeed you
streams and and are able to take
借助MapReduce可以提高效率，所以这就是重点
advantage of some efficiencies do that
MapReduce okay so this is the point at
这是所有网络流量发生的地方，这可以
which this shuffle is where all the
network traffic happens this can
实际上是海量数据，所以如果您考虑排序，那么就进行排序
actually be a vast amount of data so if
you think about sort if you're sorting
排序输出的大小与排序输入的大小相同，因此
the the output of the sort has the same
size as the input to the sort so that
表示如果您知道输入的数据量是10 TB，
means that if you're you know if your
input is 10 terabytes of data and you're
运行某种操作，您正在通过以下网络在网络上移动10 TB的数据
running a sort you're moving 10
terabytes of data across a network at
这一点，您的输出也将是10 TB，所以这是很多
this point and your output will also be
10 terabytes and so this is quite a lot
数据，然后确实来自任何MapReduce作业，尽管不是全部
of data and then indeed it is from any
MapReduce jobs although not all there's
一些在这些阶段显着减少数据量的人
some that significantly reduce the
amount of data at these stages somebody
提到了哦，如果您想将reduce的输出输入另一个
mentioned Oh what if you want to feed
the output of reduce into another
MapReduce工作确实是人们通常想要做的，
MapReduce job and indeed that was often
what people wanted to do and
如果reduce的输出可能像四类或网络一样巨大
in case the output of the reduce might
be enormous like four sort or web and
在十TB的输入上混合生产的输出
mixing the output of the produces on ten
terabytes of input the output of the
再次减少将为十兆字节，因此减少的输出也将被存储
reduces again gonna be ten terabytes so
the output of the reduce is also stored
在GFS上，您知道的系统reduce只会生成这些密钥
on GFS and the system would you know
reduce would just produce these key
值对，但MapReduce框架会收集它们并将其写入
value pairs but the MapReduce framework
would gather them up and write them into
GFS上的巨大文件，因此进行了另一轮网络通信
giant files on GFS and so there was
another round of network communication
将每个reduce的输出传递到GFS服务器所需的
required to get the output of each
reduce to the GFS server that needed to
存储减少的内容，因为您可能认为他们本可以玩
store that reduce and because you might
think that they could have played the
与将输出存储在GFS服务器上的输出相同的技巧
same trick with the output of storing
the output on the GFS server that
碰巧运行了运行Reduce的MapReduce工作者，也许他们做了
happened to run the MapReduce worker
that ran the reduce and maybe they did
这样做是因为GFS以及拆分数据以提高性能
do that but because GFS as well as
splitting data for performance also
保留两三份副本以进行容错，这意味着无论您做什么
keeps two or three copies for fault
tolerance that means no matter what you
需要通过网络将数据的一个副本写入另一台服务器
need to write one copy of the data
across a network to a different server
所以这里有很多网络通信，这里还有很多
so there's a lot of network
communication here and a bunch here also
而正是这种网络通信确实限制了
and I was this network communication
that really limited the throughput in
MapReduce于2004年在2020年因为该网络
MapReduce
in 2004 in 2020 because this network
安排是人们想要做的很多事情的限制因素
arrangement was such a limiting factor
for so many things people wanted to do
在数据中心中，现代数据中心网络从根本上要快得多
in datacenters modern data center
networks are a lot faster at the root
比以前要多，所以您可能知道一个典型的数据中心网络
than this was and so you know one
typical data center network you might
看到今天实际上有很多根而不是单个根开关
see today actually has many root instead
of a single root switch that everything
必须经历的过程中，您可能知道许多根交换机和每个机架
has to go through you might have you
know many root switches and each rack
交换机与每种复制的根交换机都有连接，并且
switch has a connection to each of these
sort of replicated root switches and the
流量在根交换机之间分配，因此现代数据中心网络
traffic is split up among the root
switches so modern data center networks
具有更高的网络吞吐量，因此，我认为
have far more network throughput and
because of that actually modern I think
Google几年前就停止使用MapReduce，但是在他们停止之前
Google sort of stopped using MapReduce a
few years ago but before they stopped
使用它，现代MapReduce实际上不再尝试在
using it the modern MapReduce actually
no longer tried to run the maps on the
与存储数据的机器相同，他们很乐意对来自
same machine as the data stored on they
were happy to vote the data from
在任何地方，因为他们只是认为这是非常快的，好的
anywhere because they just assumed that
was extremely fast okay we're out of
MapReduce的时间我们要在下一个年底结束
time for MapReduce
we have a lab due at the end of next
一个星期，你会自己写一些
week
in which you'll write your own somewhat
简化的MapReduce，所以可以玩得开心
simplified MapReduce so have fun with
that
星期四见
and see you on Thursday